[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She looked nervous, ___ her lips.",
			"optionA":"moistening",
			"optionB":"moisturing",
			"optionC":"moisturizing",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"This new water cooler is to ___ the drinking water.",
			"optionA":"purificy",
			"optionB":"purify",
			"optionC":"purity",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The directive has the aim of ___ work practices",
			"optionA":"harmonysize",
			"optionB":"harmonying",
			"optionC":"harmonising",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She was taking drugs, her eye pupils were so ___.",
			"optionA":"enlarged",
			"optionB":"inlarged",
			"optionC":"enlarging",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Several world-renowned ___ addressed the conference.",
			"optionA":"historicians",
			"optionB":"historians",
			"optionC":"historyans",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The patient had several ___ of the brain.",
			"optionA":"unnormalities",
			"optionB":"inormilities",
			"optionC":"abnormalities",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She struggled along with an ___ of clothes.",
			"optionA":"armful",
			"optionB":"armfull",
			"optionC":"armfuly",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The computer system requires several ___ checks.",
			"optionA":"maintainance",
			"optionB":"maintenance",
			"optionC":"maintanance",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He was longing for the ___ of his father.",
			"optionA":"approvity",
			"optionB":"approving",
			"optionC":"approval",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She frowned at Jackson ___.",
			"optionA":"apologetically",
			"optionB":"apologetic",
			"optionC":"apologying",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"It truly is an epic tale, ___ one of the best",
			"optionA":"aguing",
			"optionB":"arguably",
			"optionC":"arguable",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"They are revised by statutory ___ committees.",
			"optionA":"assessed",
			"optionB":"assessing",
			"optionC":"assessment",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"They weren't expecting for the ___ of the troops.",
			"optionA":"withdrawal",
			"optionB":"withdrawn",
			"optionC":"withdrawing",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I'm pushing you to ___ your perspective.",
			"optionA":"broadening",
			"optionB":"broaden",
			"optionC":"broadth",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"we aim for the ___ of the whole community.",
			"optionA":"sustanance",
			"optionB":"sustainance",
			"optionC":"sustenance",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Putting out wildfires is a very  job.",
			"optionA":"perilous",
			"optionB":"imperil",
			"optionC":"perily",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I think he behaved ___ towards you.",
			"optionA":"disgrace",
			"optionB":"disgracefully",
			"optionC":"disgraceful",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The decision does seem a little ___.",
			"optionA":"heartbreak",
			"optionB":"dishearten",
			"optionC":"heartless",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	}
]